TRONG AN PHAM

SUMMARY

As a professional with a combined experience of 5.5 years in web development, I have spent 2 years specializing in converting PSD/AI designs to HTML/CSS templates as a freelance front-end developer, and 3.5 years as a full-stack developer for an outsourcing company, mainly focusing on the front-end. With exceptional skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other relevant technologies (Node, React), I have helped numerous clients achieve their web design objectives.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, 08/2019 - 04/2023 Golden Owl Consulting - Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

- Helped team complete smooth, professional software deployments for Web applications.
- Exceeded client expectations for software function, performance and features by working closely with development and quality assurance teams.
- Wrote clean and dynamic code, leveraging expertise across multiple programming languages to meet diverse requirements.
- Integrated third-party applications into existing software, enhancing features and performance.

Freelance Web Developer, 07/2017 - 08/2019 None - Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

• Converting PSD/AI designs to HTML/CSS

Freelance Graphic Designer, 12/2016 - 06/2019 None - Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

• Design T-shirt printings

EDUCATION

Department of Information System, 2018 University of Science, HCM VNU - Ho Chi Minh City, SG

PROJECTS

E-Commerce Websites:

- KpopKart (The K-pop marketplace for all K-Pop merch)
- Giantech's GTGO: https://shop.igiantech.com/ (Shopify)
- Shevron: https://shevron.com.sg/ (Shopify)

Online course marketplace.

CONTACT

Address: Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

Phone: 0976618904

Email: phamtrongan@outlook.com

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript (Node, React)
- Web application development
- Software development life cycle
- Project documentation
- Version control
- English communication

- Nexlec: https://nexlec.com/
- Toned JP
- Eesify: https://eesify.com/

Dashboards:

- Apex Personal Wealth Management
- Merlin
- Collective AI's Healthcare Planning System
- Watchtowr

Others:

- India International Insurance
- Walla Walla
- Super Loco: https://super-loco.com/
- Golden Owl
- VNNOR (Now SynPlan)
- Golden Owl's DiSC: https://tracnghiemtinhcach.vn/
- iPoker (private poker game)